starkbros.com 2019-04-27

# Privacy Policy - Stark Bro's

Protecting your privacy is very important to us. This page describes our policies and procedures regarding the way we use, disclose, share and protect your personal information and/or data in your Stark Bro's website account. This Privacy Policy applies to activities by Stark Bro's Nurseries & Orchards Co. and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively "Stark Bro's", "we" or "us").

### What kind of information does Stark Bro's collect online?

We collect information directly from individuals, from third parties, and automatically through the Stark Bro's website.This includes the use of a third-party rating and review tool. Users of the rating and review service give consent to have their reviews and comments collected and potentially published on our website, or elsewhere. These reviews and comments can include certain biographical information such as name, alias, or location.

We use cookies, pixel tags, and other tracking technologies to automatically collect information about your activities, such as your searches, page views, date and time of your visit, and other information about your use of the Stark Bro's website. We also collect information that your computer or mobile device provides to us in connection with your use of the Stark Bro's website such as your browser type, type of computer or mobile device, IP address, mobile carrier, unique device identifier, location, and requested and referring URLs.

In addition, when you visit our website, we make use of remarketing and similar audience systems from third-party vendors, including Google and other services for Display Advertisers features, to show ads on sites across the Internet. These third-party vendors use cookies to serve ads based on past visits to our website.

### How does Stark Bro's protect my information online?

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology with verified information though DigiCert to protect your online order information as it is transmitted over the Internet. We also utilize advanced firewall technology to protect our equipment from online attacks.

Some versions of browsers and firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers like the ones we use at starkbros.com. To check the security of your Internet connection, look at your browser window after accessing our website, prior to entering your credit card information. An unbroken key icon or a closed lock icon will indicate that SSL is active. You can also double-check the security by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http:" to "https:".

If your browser or firewall does not support SSL, you will not be able to connect to the server. This also means you will not be able to mistakenly place an order through an unsecured connection. If for any reason you cannot access our secure server, you can place your order by phone at 800.325.4180.

### Do I have a choice with the use of my information?

You have the options to review, change or modify the use of your personal information in regards to promotional emails, catalog mailings, third-party sharing, and promotional telephone contact. If your account is set up online, all of these options can be found by going to _View My Account »Promotion Options_. If your account is not yet set up online, you can simply call us at 800.325.4180 to make any of these inquiries or changes. We respect your wishes concerning the use of your personal information.

You can also opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Ads Preference Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb). You can opt out of third-party vendors use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). And you can install a [browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) to opt out of Google Analytics data collection. 

### Can I resell the products I ordered?

Stark Bro's represents and warrants that our products are not eligible for resale under any circumstance. Additionally, third-party sellers are prohibited by law from any unauthorized first-sale of Stark Bro's products or misrepresentations/unauthorized use of Stark Bro's intellectual property. Violators will be held responsible.

### Have additional questions or concerns?

Should you have any additional questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us anytime. You can also contact us if you need to correct or change any account information.
